David M. Stowe Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- DMS Career Activities: Teaching and Research, 1949-1990s; Series IX
  - Courses Taught
    - Andover- Newton Theological Seminary (ANTS), 1950s-1960s, 1980s-1990s
      - China
        - Ting; TSPM: Anti- Christian China; Unity; Wang Ming Tao; Women; X-Mass (Christmas) at China; Yale- China review; Yenching faculty families (Box 146, Folder 146)
      - General
        - Academic notes, class evaluations, 1950s, 1990s (Box 147, Folder 154-173)
    - Pacific School of Religion, 1985-1986
      - History of Missions (Box 193, Folder 14)
    - Adult Sunday School Class- Presbyterian Church of Tenafly, 1968-1976
      - DMS co-leader (Box 194, Folder 18)
  - Research Projects
    - Process Theology
      - Articles, clippings, reviews; Central Atlantic Conference paper; Book notes (Box 148, Folder 174-178)
      - DMS: Thesis (pgs. 368-447); Essay: "Process Theology is Ecological Theology" (Box 148, Folder 179,180)
      - General: articles, etc. (Box 148, Folder 181-183)
      - General: articles; References; Aesthetics; Buddhism; Chinese thought; Chinese; Christ; Ecology theology; Ethics; Feminism; God (Box 149, Folder 184-196)
      - God; Hartshorne; Immortality; Liberation; Miracles; Philosophy; Pragmatism; Social science; Science; Self/soul; Teilhard; Whitehead, Alfred North; Writings, articles (Box 150, Folder 197-211)
      - Writings, materials; NCC Study Center; PSR general course; Newsletters, DMS paper; Missions; Ecology; Self; PSR; Religion (Box 151, Folder 212-222)
      - Murphy and Ellis; American theology; Bible; Creed: Statement of faith; Christ; The Cross; Church; Death; Nature/ ecology theology; Eschatology; Ethics; Evil: Theology; The Fall; Female theology; God; Acts of God; Mother God; Gospel; Heaven; Holy Spirit; Human; Hope (Box 157, Folder 276, 281-301)
      - Jesus; Justice/ judgement; Liberation; Nature; Nazarene; Practical theology; Pragmatism; Prayer; Providence; Religion; Salvation; Science; Sin; Theology; Letters, newsletter, etc.; Chinese translations; Comments of DMS: "Process Theology of Mission"; Books on Process Theology of Mission; Notes (Box 158, Folder 302-322)
      - Calvin: notes and materials; Bushnell; Edwards: notes and materials; Luther: notes and references; Various papers and notes (Box 159, Folder 323-331)
      - Notes (Box 160, Folder 332-335)
    - Interreligious Dialogue
      - Animism, nature; CME Buddhism; Buddhism (Box 152, Folder 223-230)
      - Dharma World; Christianity; Roman Catholic; Cults: Sects; Communism: Marxism; Inter-religious wants and ideas; CME Hinduism; Hinduism (Box 153, Folder 231-239)
      - Islam: clippings, articles (Box 154, Folder 240-247)
      - Islam: bridge; Islam: Christian history related to Islam: DMS paper; Japanese religion; Judaism: clippings, articles (Box 155, Folder 248-259)
      - Jews; Japanese religions: Correspondence; Mormonism; New religions; Primal religions; Sikhism; Taoism; Mission history; Lutz, Jessie: "Missionary attitudes toward indigenization within an overall context."; Indigenization; African theology; Third World theology (Box 156, Folder 260-275)
    - Vinton Project
      The "Vinton Books" are a series of compiled biographical information about missionaries who served under the American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions. DMS was working on a project to update the Vinton volumes, using information from Board personnel files.
      - Completed added entry forms: A, B, 1992 (Box 202, Folder 1-2)
      - Information from UCBWM Personnel cards: C-Z, 1992 (Box 202, Folder 3-8)
      - Completed added entry forms: S-Z, 1992 (Box 202, Folder 8)
      - Vinton indexes and list of names missing for which cards are available (Box 203, Folder 9)
      - Photocopied samples of UCBWM Personnel cards: A (Box 203, Folder 10)
      - Biographical information from notebook labeled "ABCFM Missionaries to 1957" (Box 203, Folder 11)
      - Numbers of missionary personnel by country, 1945-1960 (Box 203, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence with Tom Nelson (son-in-law) regarding computer database for project, 1993-1994 (Box 204, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence regarding earlier database by C. Miller, 1987-1990 (Box 204, Folder 14)
      - Photocopies of Vinton Volume I (incomplete) (Box 204, Folder 15)
      - Photocopies of Vinton Volume II (incomplete) (Box 204, Folder 16)
- Personal Items and Memorabilia, 1911-2000; Series X
  This series includes biographical information about Stowe, slides that he took on his various travels, and a number of interesting collected artifacts.
  - Appointment books
    - Appointments, etc., 1973-1977, 1980-1983 (Box 205, Folder 1-3)
    - Appointments, etc., 1983-1985 (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Chronological file of biographical documentation
    - Statements, summaries, 1956-1984 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Various documents and correspondence, 1942-1995, n.d. (Box 206, Folder 6-10)
    - Testimonials, tributes: Farewell letters for retirement, 1984-1985 (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - Testimonials, tributes, 1952-1956, n.d. (Box 207, Folder 12)
  - Slides
    - Africa
      - Scanned slides
        - A – Victoria Falls (10 slides) B - Ghana (5 slides) C - Chiruaramani (2 slides) D – Wedding (7 slides) E - Gazaland (21 slides) F – Mt. Silinda (12 slides) G - Harare (14 slides) H – Family Farms (7 slides) J – Kafue (13 slides) K – Ghana (34 slides) L – Mindalo (11 slides) M - Lusaka (9 slides) N – Wanze (5 slides) O – Egypt – Sudan (17 slides) P – Airports (2 slides) Q – Amboseli (14 slides) R – Uganda (38 slides) S – WCC Reception (30 slides) T – Uganda (26 slides) U – AACC 1963 (21 slides) V – AACC 1963 (8 slides) W – Meheba (26 slides) X – To Meheba (26 slides) Y – Kalume (10 slides) (Box 209)
      - Slides not scanned
        - Nairobi, Kilimanjaro, Africa game, Masai Court, South Africa, Chikore Station, WCC Plenary, Kenya, n.d.
    - China
      - Scanned slides
        - Group III A – Guilin (27 slides) B – Yangshuo (15 slides) C – Li Jiang (95 slides) D – Li Jiang continued (63 slides) E – Temple (25 slides) F – Minorities (12 slides) G – Stone Forest (13 slides) H – Yunnan (70 slides) J – Guangsi (15 slides) K – Chengdu (42 slides) L – Sichuan (25 slides) M – ? Dam (31 slides) N – Chengtu (19 slides) O – China – maps/charts (6 slides) P – Hai (78 slides) Q – Circus (12 slides) R – Commune (11 slides) (Box 210)
        - Group V A – Air Views (4 slides) B – Chungqing (17 slides) D – Yangtze A (18 slides) E – Shikaozai (19 slides) F – Yangtze B (8 slides) G – Baidicheng (23 slides) H – Yangzte after Baidicheng (56 slides) I – Fengjie (8 slides) J – Gezhouba to Wuhan (37 slides) K – Wuhan (20 slides) L – Wuhan Museum (12 slides) M – Hong Kong (71 slides) N – Hong Kong continued (34 slides) O – Hong Kong continued (42 slides) P – Tao Feng Shan (13 slides) Q – Hong Kong Christian Service (33 slides) R – Hong Kong Views (15 slides) W – Markets (6 slides) Y – Homes (2 slides) (Box 210)
    - Europe
      - Scanned slides
        - Group I A – Enfant ? (29 slides) B – Rastach (53 slides) C – Worms (21 slides) D – Bern and Rhine (10 slides) E – Berlin (33 slides) F – Loccum (28 slides) G – Russia (23 slides) (Box 210)
        - Group 1 H – Holland (21 slides) I – Amsterdam (25 slides) J – Cambridge (29 slides) K – Canterbury (27 slides) L – Swanwich (20 slides) M – Italy (11 slides) N – Florence Festival (24 slides) O – Florence (23 slides) P – To Prague (9 slides) Q – Prague (29 slides) R – Sofia (16 slides) S – Eisleben (10 slides) T – Leipzig (12 slides) U – Wittenberg (14 slides) V – Greenland/Iceland (8 slides) W – Portugal (32 slides) X- Portugal (9 slides) Y – London (65 slides) Z – Bielefeld (6 slides) (Box 211)
        - A – Erfurt (20 slides) B – E. Berlin (17 slides) C – Tong (?) (14 slides) (Box 211)
      - Slides not scanned
        - Include: Uppsala, Stockholm, Denmark, Ely Cathedral, Scotland, France, Frankfurt, Berlin, Switzerland (Box 211)
    - Latin America
      - Scanned slides
        - Group I A – Tegucigalpa (5 slides) B – Honduras (13 slides) C – Honduras – cucumbers (8 slides) D – Cayales (20 slides) E – Nicaragua (16 slides) F – Nicaragua cotton farm (12 slides) G – Mexico (7 slides) H – Mexico church (14 slides) J – Mexico west coast (31 slides) K – Belize (2 slides) L - Mexico (7 slides) M - Mexico (23 slides) N – Mexico (39 slides) O – Argentina (12 slides) P – Ecuador (21 slides) (Box 211)
        - Group 1 Q – Mexico-Xochicalco (10 slides) R – Mexico- Countryside (11 slides) S – Mexico- Cuernavaca (9 slides) T – Honduras (75 slides) (Box 212)
      - Slides not scanned
        - Include: Ecuador, Colombia, Costa Rica, Haiti (Box 212)
    - Middle East
      - Slides scanned
        - Group I A – To Jerusalem (69 slides) B – Jesus (5 slides) C – Jerusalem (54 slides) D – To Jericho (48 slides) E – Rahlus? (3 slides) F – Judea (52 slides) G – Galilee (13 slides) H – Bethlehem (11 slides) J – Galilee (10 slides) K – Nazareth (11 slides) L – Biazert (5 slides) M – Chacoun (7 slides) (Box 212)
      - Slides not scanned
        - Include: Athens, Beirut, Lebanon, Turkey, Near East School of Theology, Jordan, Sidon, Tyre, Syria (Box 212)
        - Turkey, Greece (Box 212)
    - South Asia
      - Slides scanned
        - Group V A – Sri Lanka (81 slides) B – Jaffna (24 slides) C - Tamilnad (33 slides) D - Hyderbad (10 slides) E – India (13 slides) F – Riggs Clinic (9 slides) G – Agra (29 slides) H – Punjab (6 slides) J – Minar (16 slides) K – ND-PTS (29 slides) L – Delhi (30 slides) M - Bakahtapur (5 slides) N – Nepal (27 slides) O – Kathmandu (19 slides) P – Kathmandu (24 slides) (Box 213)
      - Slides not scanned
        - Include: Bombay, India, Indira Gandhi, Punjab, Pasumalai, Hyderabad, Delhi, Madurai, Calcutta (Box 213)
    - South East Asia / Asia
      - Miscellaneous slides, not scanned. (Box 214)
    - Ecumenical / Board-related
      - Miscellaneous groups and events (Box 215)
      - Possible illustrations for proposed history of Board by DMS (Box 215)
  - Collected Material
    - Fur robe presented to the Rev. John A. Mac Coll of Kingwilliamstown, South Africa by King Khama, Paramount Chief of the Bamangwato on the occasion of Mr. Mac Coll's visit to Khama's capital, Serowe on October 19, 1911. (Box OV1)
      Consists of 30 skins of the ingada or wildcat sewn together; inscription on skins.
- Addendum - 2011, 1881-2001; Series XI
  - Correspondence
    - Family
      - Constance and Elyn[?], 1974-1992 (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - "China Mail", 1942-1950 (Box 217, Folder 2-6)
    - Personal
      - Alden-Davis, 1976-1993 (Box 217, Folder 7)
      - Donaldson, 1971-1973 (Box 217, Folder 8)
      - Donaldson, 1974-1999 (Box 218, Folder 9-12)
      - Donaldson-Hunzinger, 1973-1999 (Box 218, Folder 13)
      - Kelly-Xie, 1960-1995 (Box 218, Folder 14)
      - Takenaka, Masao, 1990s - 2000 (Box 208, Folder 1)
      - Retirement letters and cards, 1984-1985 (Box 218, Folder 15)
    - General
      - Letters re human rights, 1980-1981 (Box 218, Folder 16)
  - Sermons, Lectures, and Talks by David M. Stowe
    - Sermons
      - "The Essence of Faith", 1958 (Box 219, Folder 23)
      - "What Destiny for Christianity?", 1967 (Box 219, Folder 24)
      - "Some Reflections on 50 Years of Ministry", 1993 (Box 219, Folder 25)
    - Prayers
      - Noon prayers, 1950s-1970s (Box 219, Folder 26)
      - Calls to worship/silence, n.d. (Box 219, Folder 27)
    - Talks
      - China speech notes, 1950s (Box 219, Folder 28)
      - "China: Mirror and Model for the World", 1977 (Box 219, Folder 29)
      - Jewish-Christian-Muslim Forum, 1978 (Box 219, Folder 30)
  - Writings
    - Books, Booklets, and Pamphlets
      - "What is Christian Witness?", 1962 (Box 220, Folder 31)
      - "Why Mission Today?, late 1960s (Box 220, Folder 32)
      - "Year 175", 1985 (Box 220, Folder 33)
    - Articles in Journals
      - "Six Lessons from Red China", 1951 (Box 220, Folder 34)
      - "The Interplay of Missions and Theology" (ms.), 1960 (Box 220, Folder 35)
      - "China and the Protestant Ethic", 1999 (Box 220, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous Writings
      - "The Nature and Activity of God", 1941 (Box 220, Folder 37)
      - "Pro Mundi Vita", 1969 (Box 220, Folder 38)
      - "Global Consciousness and Human Development", 1970s (Box 220, Folder 39)
      - "The Church in China", 1979 (Box 220, Folder 40)
      - "It is finished" (unpublished), 1993 (Box 220, Folder 41)
  - Resource Files: ABCFM/UCBWM Geographical Files
    - Africa
      - General - photos, 1960s-1970s (Box 220, Folder 42)
      - General - documents, 1945-1948 (Box 220, Folder 43)
      - Angola - photos, 1960s-1971 (Box 220, Folder 44-46)
      - Ghana - photos, 1950s-1960s (Box 221, Folder 47)
      - Rhodesia - photos, 1960s (Box 221, Folder 48)
      - Rhodesia, 1960s-1970s (Box 221, Folder 49-50)
      - South Africa - photos, 1950s-1960s (Box 221, Folder 51-52)
      - South Africa - 23rd Ps. in Zulu, 1939 (Box 221, Folder 53)
      - South Africa - papers on "Non-European Nurses in South Africa before 1944", 1930s-1970s (Box 221, Folder 54)
      - South Africa: Inanda Seminary photos, 1960s (Box 221, Folder 55)
      - South Africa: Inanda Seminary photos, 1960s (Box 222, Folder 56)
      - South Africa: Inanda Seminary brochure, 1968 (Box 222, Folder 57)
      - Zambia - Theological Education by Extension workbooks, n.d. (Box 222, Folder 58-60)
      - Zimbabwe - photos, 1950s-1960s (Box 222, Folder 61)
      - Zimbabwe - Shona course text, n.d. (Box 222, Folder 62)
    - Asia
      - China - Lyda Houston's "A Pictured Record of 26 Years", 1924-1950 (Box 223, Folder 63)
      - China - photos and related material (Josie Horn), 1919-1941 (Box 223, Folder 64)
      - China - Catholicism (articles and notes), 1960s-1990s (Box 223, Folder 65)
      - China - history (misc. documents), 1927-2001 (Box 223, Folder 66)
      - China - Hong Kong history: "The future of the Past" by Noah Fehl, 1966 (Box 223, Folder 67)
      - China - missions (papers by Dorothea Coryell), 1978 (Box 223, Folder 68)
      - China - Tsai, Yong-Chun book, 1997 (Box 223, Folder 69)
      - India - phtotos and slides, 1960s-1980s (Box 223, Folder 70)
      - India - Baur, Alby ms., "Even Me?" (Box 223, Folder 71)
      - India - White, Emmons Memoirs, 1959 (Box 224, Folder 72)
      - Japan - Mission Contribution Certificate, 1881 (Box 224, Folder 73)
    - Europe
      - Greece - Mansfield, L.: typescript: "The History of Pierce College, Athens, Greece 1878-1970" (Box 224, Folder 74)
    - Latin America
      - Mexico - photos, n.d. (Box 224, Folder 75)
    - Near East
      - General - photos, 1960s (Box 224, Folder 76)
      - General - English workbook in Arabic, n.d. (Box 224, Folder 77)
      - General - Stone, Frank papers, 1970-1980 (Box 224, Folder 78)
      - Armenia - book on Eastern Orthodoxy, 1963 (Box 224, Folder 79)
      - Lebanon - Haigazian College catalogue, 1962-1964 (Box 224, Folder 80)
      - Lebanon - UN report, 1962 (Box 224, Folder 81)
      - Turkey - Gazientep photos, 1959 (Box 224, Folder 82)
      - Turkey - Talas School photos, 1962 (Box 224, Folder 83)
      - Turkey - Matteson, Roger ms., "My Years in Turkey, 1923-1927", 1982 (Box 224, Folder 84)
      - Turkey - Scott, Harold ms., "The History of Robert College", n.d. (Box 224, Folder 85)
      - Turkey - Tarsus American College yearbook, 1964 (Box 224, Folder 86)
      - Turkey - Tarsus American College yearbooks, 1966, 1967 (Box 225, Folder 87-88)
      - Turkey Development Foundation: International Evaluation Report, 1983 (Box 225, Folder 89)
      - Turkey - UCBWM Turkish book collection inventory, 1979 (Box 225, Folder 90)
    - North America
      - Hawaii - photos and misc. pamphlets (Box 225, Folder 91)
    - Oceania/Micronesia
      - Micronesia - photo book, n.d. (Box 225, Folder 92)
  - Resource Files: ABCFM/UCBWM Documents and Collected Materials
    - UCBWM Records
      - Archives Inventory (NY), ca.2000 (Box 225, Folder 93-94)
      - Meetings, 1957-1961 (Box 226, Folder 95)
      - Handbook for Missionaries and Mission Organizations of the ABCFM, 1949 (Box 226, Folder 96)
      - Manual for Board of International Missions of the Evangelical and Reformed Church, 1953 (Box 226, Folder 97)
      - Missionary Packet, 1985 (Box 226, Folder 98)
      - Pamphlet, 1971 (Box 226, Folder 99)
      - Rules of Board of Directors, 1961-1966 (Box 226, Folder 100)
      - Staff photos, mid-1960s (Box 226, Folder 101)
      - Structure report, 1966 (Box 226, Folder 102)
      - Vault records and related correspondence, 1990s (Box 226, Folder 103)
      - UCC Mission Personnel Conference, 1982-1983 (Box 226, Folder 104)
      - UCC structure report, 1969 (Box 226, Folder 105)
      - Staff and Salaries Committee, 1968-1975 (Box 226, Folder 106-111)
      - Staff and Salaries Committee, 1976-1980 (Box 227, Folder 112-117)
      - Staff and Salaries Committee, 1981-1984 (Box 228, Folder 118-121)
      - Staff and Salaries Committee: Miscellaneous letters, 1971-1972 (Box 228, Folder 122)
      - Staff and Salaries Committee: Salaries, 1971-1983 (Box 228, Folder 123)
      - Staff and Salaries Committee: Regional Secretary, 1974-19846 (Box 228, Folder 124)
      - Staff and Salaries Committee: Stenhouse papers, 1977-1984 (Box 228, Folder 125-126)
    - Collected Materials
      - Books and Manuscripts
        - Bartholomew, Alan: tyepscript: "The Mission Field Which Will Not Die", 1985 (Box 228, Folder 127)
        - Carleton Festschrift: "Mission in a Post Colonial World" (vol. of papers), n.d. (Box 229, Folder 128)
        - Corr, Donald: dissertation: "The Field is the World", n.d. (Box 229, Folder 129)
        - Dunlap, Mary: typescript: "The Woman's Boards", n.d. (Box 229, Folder 130)
        - Johnson, Luke, ed., "Teaching Religion to Undergraduates", 1973 (Box 229, Folder 131)
        - Maxfield, Charles: dissertation: "The Presbyterian and Congregational Churches among the Dakota", 1991 (Box 229, Folder 132)
        - Schneider, Robert: dissertation: "The Senior Secretary", 1980 (Box 229, Folder 133-134)
        - Sithole, N.: handwritten manuscript: "Fighting from Her Majesty's Prison", 1966 (Box 230, Folder 135)
        - Sithole, N.: typescript: "Fighting from Her Majesty's Prison", 1966 (Box 230, Folder 136-138)
        - Sithole, N.: handwritten manuscript: "Obed Muetzo" (Box 230, Folder 139)
        - Sithole, N.: typescript: "Obed Muetzo", n.d. (Box 231, Folder 140)
        - Sithole, N.: typescript: "Polygamist", n.d. (Box 231, Folder 141)
        - Strong, Robbins, "Three Transitional Years:1934-1937: Life in Shansi China", 1987 (Box 231, Folder 142)
        - Stuckey-Kauffman, P. dissertation: "For the Sake of Unity", 1985 (Box 231, Folder 143)
        - Von Gruenigen, A., "The Middle Sectors as a Political Force in Mexico", n.d. (Box 231, Folder 144)
      - Periodicals
        - China Bulletin, 1947-1950 (Box 231, Folder 145-146)
        - China Bulletin, 1951-1962 (Box 232, Folder 147-157)
        - China Focus, 1990-1998 (Box 232, Folder 158-159)
        - China Insight, 1992-1997 (Box 233, Folder 160)
        - Pray for China Fellowship, 1991-1999 (Box 233, Folder 161)
        - U.S. Catholic China Bureau, 1989-1994 (Box 233, Folder 162)
        - David M. Stowe notes on periodical articles, 1980s (Box 233, Folder 163)
      - Articles, Reports, and Related Papers
        - ABCFM almanac and yearbook, 1910, 1948 (Box 233, Folder 164)
        - Gill article about David M. Stowe, 1968 (Box 233, Folder 165)
        - Miscellaneous articles, 1966-1988 (Box 233, Folder 166)
        - NACCATEA meeting report, 1964 (Box 233, Folder 167)
        - WSCF conference report, 1911 (Box 233, Folder 168)
  - David M. Stowe Activities: Church and Ecumenical
    - National Council of Churches of Christ, U.S.A., Department of Overseas Ministries
      - China Program, 1965-1970 (Box 233, Folder 169-170)
      - China Program, 1971-1984 (Box 234, Folder 171-174)
      - China Program - re Human Nature, 1962-1976 (Box 234, Folder 175)
      - Executive Committee Reports - reports, 1963 (Box 234, Folder 176)
      - Executive Committee - reports, 1981-1982 (Box 234, Folder 177)
      - Other programs and committees: Amity Foundation, 1985-1997 (Box 235, Folder 178)
      - Other programs and committees: "Thinking Occasions", 1965-1969 (Box 235, Folder 179-180)
    - World Council of Churches
      - Conference files: Mexico, 1963 (Box 235, Folder 181-182)
      - Conference files: Nairobi, 1975 (Box 235, Folder 183)
      - Conference files: Nairobi, 1975-1976 (Box 236, Folder 184-185)
      - Conference files: Melbourne, 1980 (Box 236, Folder 186-189)
      - Conference files: Melbourne, 1980 (Box 237, Folder 190-193)
    - United Church of Christ, 1971-1983
      - General Synod 8, 1971 (Box 237, Folder 194)
      - General Synod 9, 1973 (Box 237, Folder 195)
      - General Synod 10, 1975 (Box 237, Folder 196)
      - General Synod 11, 1977 (Box 238, Folder 197-199)
      - General Synod 12, 1979 (Box 238, Folder 200-201)
      - General Synod 13, 1981 (Box 239, Folder 202-204)
      - General Synod 14, 1983 (Box 239, Folder 205-206)
  - Personal Items and Memorabilia
    - General
      - Chinese books (miscellaneous), n.d. (Box 240, Folder 207)
      - Chinese children's books, n.d. (Box 240, Folder 208)
      - Christmas memorabilia, n.d. (Box 240, Folder 209)
      - History of religions poster-chart, n.d. (Box 240, Folder 210)
      - Photos of Universal Christian Conference on Life and Work, Stockholm, 1925; identifications for Chinese National Christian Council meeting photographs from 1935 (no photo); unidentified photo blocks, 1925, 1935, n.d. (Box 240, Folder 211)
      - Large scale etching: "Panorama of the Bosphorus" (Box OVd1)
      - Who's Who in International Missions pamphlets, 1938, 1949 (Box 240, Folder 212)
    - Personal Research Catalogue
      - Category index (Box 240, Folder 213)
      - Index for general articles (Box 240, Folder 214)
      - Index for Religion articles (Box 240, Folder 215)
      - A, n.d. (Box 241, Folder 216)
      - B, n.d. (Box 241, Folder 217)
      - C, n.d. (Box 241, Folder 218)
      - D, n.d. (Box 241, Folder 219)
      - F, n.d. (Box 241, Folder 220)
      - G, n.d. (Box 241, Folder 221)
      - H, n.d. (Box 241, Folder 222)
      - I, n.d. (Box 241, Folder 223)
      - L, n.d. (Box 241, Folder 224)
      - Luther, n.d. (Box 241, Folder 225)
      - M, n.d. (Box 241, Folder 226)
      - Mission, n.d. (Box 241, Folder 227)
      - N, n.d. (Box 241, Folder 228)
      - Orthodox mission, n.d. (Box 241, Folder 229)
      - P, n.d. (Box 241, Folder 230)
      - R, n.d. (Box 241, Folder 231)
      - S, n.d. (Box 242, Folder 232)
      - T, n.d. (Box 242, Folder 233)
      - V, n.d. (Box 242, Folder 234)
      - W, n.d. (Box 242, Folder 235)
      - Z, n.d. (Box 242, Folder 236)
      - "Disordered notes", n.d. (Box 242, Folder 237)
      - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 242, Folder 238)
    - Portraits
      - David M. Stowe, 1950s-1980s (Box 242, Folder 239)
    - Audio Items and Related Papers
      - Cassette: "175 Unbelievable Years": history of the UCBWM by David M. Stowe, 1985 (Box 242, Folder 240)
      - Cassette: "First Fruits: 20 Chinese Hymns", n.d. (Box 242, Folder 241)
      - Oral history of David M. Stowe's life by David M. Stowe (audio cassette and 2-CD set), 1998 (Box 243, Folder 242)
      - Cassette: Salem slide show audio, n.d. (Box 243, Folder 243)
      - Cassette: Ting, K.H. (Bishop) interview, 1973 (Box 243, Folder 244)
      - Cassette and CD: "The Sending and the Sent" narrated by David M. Stowe, 1960 (Box 243, Folder 245)
      - 33 1/3 rpm record: "The Sending and the Sent" narrated by David M Stowe; 33 1/3 rpm record from UCBWM General Synod, 1960, n.d. (Box OVd1)
    - Slides